Rewind and love again.
Press Play is a music, romance, science fiction film directed by Greg Björkman.
Laura and Harrison have the picture-perfect romance built on
the foundation of a shared love of music.
After a deadly accident, Laura gets the chance to save the love of her life when
she discovers that their mixtape can transport her back in time.
Laura, played by Clara Rugaard.
Harrison, played by Lewis Pullman.
Cooper, played by Danny Glover.
Chloe, played by Lyrica Okano.
Mrs. Knott, played by Christina Chang.
Mr. Knott, played by Matt Walsh.
Press Play is a 2022 science fiction romantic drama film written by Greg Björkman and James
Bachelor, and directed by Björkman in his directorial debut, from a story by Josh Boone.
It stars Clara Rugaard, Lewis Pullman, Lyrica Okano,
Christina Chang, Matt Walsh, and Danny Glover.
It was shot on Oahu.
The film was released in the United States on June 24, 2022, by The Avenue.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of time travel, time, destiny, music.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.